htcwiki.com 2006-08-23

# Privacy - htcwiki

Last Updated: 3/3/2006

htcwiki is powered by Wetpaint and subject to the Terms and Conditions on this site.

## Wetpaint.com, Inc. ("Wetpaint") Privacy Policy

At Wetpaint, we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our users. This privacy policy explains Wetpaint's privacy practices for our Web sites, including those of this Web site located at [http://www.htcwiki.com](http://www.htcwiki.com/) ("Sites"), for users of our services. By using any of our Sites, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy.

## What is Personal Information?

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as a user name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual’s activities when directly linked to that person. Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you.

## Personal Information We Collect

You may provide personal information to us in a number of ways when you visit our Sites. For example, depending on the specific web site, you may provide us with personal information when you:

  1. Register as a member and set up an account;
  2. Subscribe to email notification of certain changes in Site functionality or content (e.g., page changes); or
  3. Contact us by email for any reason (such as to request customer service or provide us with your comments/feedback). We collect your name and email address in this manner.

Please note that we are not responsible for any personal information that you voluntarily provide as part of any edits or similar submissions to the Sites and we discourage you from doing so, as such information is publicly available.

When you visit our Sites, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and the time and date of your visit and Site pages visited. This information is collected through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer by a web site to give you a unique identification. We use cookies on our Sites to help optimize your online experience. For example, we use cookies to track your editing of, and submissions to, our Sites. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the personally identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.

Wetpaint does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality on our Sites may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

## How We Use Personal Information

In general, we may use personal information to process your requests or transactions and provide you with high-quality services or to inform you about other products or services we think will be of interest. For example, we use your information to provide online editing and publishing services to you, and to display customized content and advertising. We may also use personal information for certain auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve Wetpaint technologies and services. Your personal information may also be used to set up or contact you regarding your account. When we use your personal information, it may be processed on our services in the United States of America and in other countries, and your information may be processed on a server that lies outside your own country.

When we use personal information in our internal marketing efforts, we provide you with choices (see Choice below) and do not disclose the information to third parties except as described in this privacy policy.

We may receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, and will combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you. In such cases, this privacy policy governs this information.

## Use of Aggregate Information

Personal information does not include “aggregate” information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new services and tailor existing services to customer desires. We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of Wetpaint.

## Sharing of Personal Information

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this privacy policy. We share personal information with third-party vendors and contractors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing data and providing marketing assistance. We require our third party vendors to only use the information for the purpose it was provided. We are not responsible for any additional information you provide directly to third parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.

We also reserve the right to disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this privacy policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety; to prevent or protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of our Sites; to ensure the security of our network and services; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

In addition, information about our users, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of the company.

## Links to Other Web Sites

Our Sites contain links to other web sites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. Except as described above, we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of web sites to which we link. Links from Sites to third parties or to other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

## Use of the Sites by Children

We encourage parents to take an active interest in their children's use of the Internet. We do not intend to collect information from children who are under 13 years of age. If you are under 13, you will not be allowed to register for our service and you should not provide information on our Sites.

## Security

We have put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to protect personal information while it is under our control. For example, your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information on such sites, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our Sites by any person using your password. Please contact us immediately if you believe your password has been misused.

## Choice

To opt-out of receiving communications from us or to request that we correct or delete your personal information, please contact us, or edit your online profile settings on this website.

## Policy Changes

We will modify this privacy policy from time to time as our privacy practices keep up to date with technology and legal developments. We will notify you of the changes by posting the new policy on our Sites and indicating at the top of the privacy policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review our privacy policy each time you visit our Sites to see if it has been updated since your last visit and to make sure you understand how the information that you provide will be used.

## Your Comments or Concerns

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us.
